Guide to the David Price Papers, 1960-2006 and undated RL.01048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Congressional Papers Record Group, 1981-1994 and undated
  - Legislative Files Series, 1981-1994, bulk 1987-1994 and undated, 66 boxes
    - Education and Labor Subseries, 1985-1994 and undated
      - Higher Education Act
        - Dell Grants for Prisoners, 1992 (Box CLE-25)
        - Talking Points, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-25)
      - Foreign Language, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-25)
      - Libraries, 1993 (Box CLE-25)
      - Literacy, 1986-1993 (Box CLE-25)
      - Literacy-National Literacy Act, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-25)
      - Literacy Task Force, 1991 (Box CLE-25)
      - Longer School Year, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-25)
      - Math and Science, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-25)
      - NASFAA [National Association of Student Financial Aid Administrators], 1987 and undated (Box CLE-25)
      - NEA [National Education Association], 1991-1992 (Box CLE-26)
      - National Governors Association, 1990 (Box CLE-26)
      - NSBA [National School Boards Association], 1991-1992 (Box CLE-26)
      - National Service Act 1990, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-26)
      - National Service, 1988-1991 (Box CLE-26)
      - National Service-Clinton, 1993, 2 folders (Box CLE-26)
      - National Service-Vista, 1993 (Box CLE-26)
      - National Writing Project, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-26)
      - NCAA [National Collegiate Athletic Association], 1991 (Box CLE-26)
      - NCAE, 1989 (Box CLE-26)
      - N.C. School Food Service Association, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-26)
      - OERI [Office of Educational Research and Improvement], 1992-1993 (Box CLE-26)
      - PTA, 1993 (Box CLE-26)
      - Rehabilitation Act, 1992 (Box CLE-26)
      - PAT [Parents as Teachers], 1992 (Box CLE-26)
      - Women, 1989-1992 (Box CLE-26)
      - Savings Bonds, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-26)
      - Sex Education, 1991 (Box CLE-26)
      - Standardized Tests, 1990-1992, 2 folders (Box CLE-26)
      - Statistics, 1991 (Box CLE-27)
      - SCAN [Student Counseling and Assistance Network], 1991-1992 (Box CLE-27)
      - School Improvement, 1992 (Box CLE-27)
      - Student Loan Affordability Act, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-27)
      - Taft Institute, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-27)
      - Teacher Issues, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-27)
      - Tech Prep Program, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-27)
      - Technology in the Classroom, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-27)
      - TRIO, 1993 and undated (Box CLE-27)
      - USSA [United States Student Association], 1993 and undated (Box CLE-27)
      - Vocational Education, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-27)
      - Vocational Education-American Vocational Association, [199-] (Box CLE-27)
      - Ready to Learn, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box CLE-27)
      - AAUW [American Association of University Women], 1991 (Box CLE-27)
      - Adult Education, 1991 (Box CLE-27)
      - HBCU's (Historically Black Colleges and Universities), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-27)
      - Blind, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-27)
      - The Carolina Literacy Center, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-27)
      - Chapter I [grants], 1992 (Box CLE-27)
      - Chapter I-Education Equity Act, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-27)
      - Community Colleges, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-27)
      - Sci/Tech Hearing [Scientific and Technical Literacy], 1987 (Box CLE-27)
      - Sci/Tech: HBCU [Federal Science and Technology Support for Historically Black Colleges and Universities] Hearing 10/9/87, 1987 (Box CLE-28)
      - Literacy: Testimony, Field Hearing, Joint Economic Committee, 1987, Sept. (Box CLE-28)
      - Literacy: Testimony, Sci/Tech Field Hearing (1987 Nov.), 1987 (Box CLE-28)
      - Breakfast [Meeting with David T. Kearns/Workforce Literacy Task Force], 1991 (Box CLE-28)
      - Literacy: Nan Bell's Notes, 1988 and undated (Box CLE-28)
      - Workforce Literacy Legislative Summit, 1989, 2 folders (Box CLE-28)
      - Literacy Bill, 1985-1990, 1-4 of 5 folders (Box CLE-28)
      - Literacy Bill, 1985-1990, 5 of 5 folders (Box CLE-29)
      - Literacy, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box CLE-29)
      - Literacy-RTP [Research Triangle Park] Hearing Nov. 1987, 1987 (Box CLE-29)
      - Literacy Report-General Background, 1986-1988 (Box CLE-29)
      - Congressional Study on Literacy in the South, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box CLE-29)
      - Infant Mortality, 1988-1990 (Box CLE-29)
      - WIC [the Special Supplemental Food Program for Women, Infants, and Children], 1987-1992 (Box CLE-29)
      - 1990 Day Care Act, 1987-1990, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box CLE-29)
      - 1990 Day Care Act, 1987-1990, 3 of 3 folders (Box CLE-30)
      - Higher Education Field Hearing, 1991 (Box CLE-30)
      - Panels #1-#4 [Field Hearing on the Reauthorization of the Higher Education Act], 1991, 4 folders (Box CLE-30)
      - Shaw University-Estey Hall, 1987, 2 folders (Box CLE-30)
      - Wake County Public Library-Literacy Grant, 1987 (Box CLE-30)
      - S and T Literacy Conference, 1987 (Box CLE-30)
      - S and T: Literacy Bill History, 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box CLE-30)
      - Family Medical Leave Act-HR 2, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-31)
      - Farm Workers, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Indian JTPA [Job Training Partnership Act] Programs, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Mine Safety/Health, undated (Box CLE-31)
      - OSHA [Occupational Safety and Health Administration], 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Older Workers Benefits Protection Act 1990, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - HCR 92-OSHA Regulations for Forklifts, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Paper Work Reduction Act, 1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation, 1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Railroad Retirement, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - RICO [Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations], 1987-1989 (Box CLE-31)
      - Labor-Striker Replacement-HR 5, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Unemployment-HR 4727/HR 5260-Downey, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Unemployment, 1990 (Box CLE-31)
      - Workplace Monitoring, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Workplace Leave Flexibility, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Family Support-Child Welfare, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Child Abuse, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - CASA [Court-Appointed Special Advocate?], 1993 and undated (Box CLE-31)
      - Day Care, 1990 (Box CLE-31)
      - Disabled Children, 1989-1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Family Preservation Act, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Head Start, 1990-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Arc of North Carolina, 1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Head Start-Randolph County, 1990-1993, 2 folders (Box CLE-31)
      - Hunger-World Bank, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Hunger Committee, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Poverty, 1988-1991 (Box CLE-31)
      - Urban Policy, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-31)
      - Welfare Jobs, 1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Welfare Microenterprises, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-31)
      - Women in the Workplace, 1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - WIC [Women, Infants, and Children], 1991-1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - General Children's Information, 1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Childcare, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Green Thumb-Employment and Training, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Mayview Convalescent Center, 1992 and undated (Box CLE-32)
      - OAA [Older Americans Act], Council on Aging, 1989-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - UNC [University of North Carolina] School of Medicine-Aging, 1991 (Box CLE-32)
      - Seniors Luncheon, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Speeches and Talking Points, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - League of Women Voters, 1991 (Box CLE-32)
      - Wake County School System Magnet Schools, 1989-1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Marketplace [Conference?], 1989-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Microenterprises, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Small Business and Regulations, 1994 (Box CLE-32)
      - Small Business Legislation, 1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - ERISA [Employee Retirement Income Security Act] Reform, 1991 (Box CLE-32)
      - DP's Small Business Letters, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - SBTDC [Small Business and Technology Development Center], 1992-1994 (Box CLE-32)
      - Small Business Hearing 5/6-Liability Insurance, 1987-1988 (Box CLE-32)
      - N.C. Rural Economic Development Center, 1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Small Business Procurement Center, 1987-1988 (Box CLE-32)
      - Teamwork for Employees-Management, 1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Undercharge Rates, 1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Labor-Major Legislation of 102nd Congress, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Beck Decision, undated (Box CLE-32)
      - Child Labor, 1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Coal Industry Retiree Health Benefit, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Davis-Bacon, 1989-1992 (Box CLE-32)
      - Education: State Student Incentive Grant, 1993 (Box CLE-32)
      - Wake County Public Schools-Adolescent Family Life Demonstration Project, 1987 (Box CLE-32)
    - Energy and Commerce Subseries, 1987-1994
      Contains documents related to a variety of topics, chiefly energy production and the environment. Issues and legislative initiatives vary widely but often relate to the environment, including the following topics: clean air and wilderness; animal welfare; public health; cancer hospitals; the FDA [Food and Drug Administration]; various medications; maternal-child programs; Medicare; insurance and other health-related issues; cable television; telecommunications; energy and utility issues; nuclear power legislation; and energy policies. There is less correspondence and a higher frequency of staff memos to Price, perhaps reflecting less activity in this area of legislation.
      Prominent organizations in these files include: the EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] or environment-related organizations such as the Environmental Defense Fund; certain North Carolina organizations; UNC [University of North Carolina]; the State of North Carolina; North Carolina State University; the FCC; telecommunications companies; public radio; and CPandL [Carolina Power and Light].
      As in previous subseries, correspondence frequently reveals evidence of legislators attempting to gain support for their initiative. The files are unarranged.
      - Speeches/Talking Points, 1988-1993, 2 folders (Box CLE-33)
      - Alamance County Landfill, 1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - Circle of Poison [Prevention Act] (102), 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Clean Air/NC (103), 1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] at RTP [Research Triangle Park], 1990 and undated (Box CLE-33)
      - EPA Lab Move (103), 1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Fontana Lake/Swain County, 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Global Warming/HR 4750 (102), 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - National Institute for the Environment (103), 1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - Pacific Northwest Forests (102), undated (Box CLE-33)
      - Indoor Air/Smoking (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Pesticides/Delaney Clause, 1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - Payments in Lieu of Taxes (101), 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Southern Appalachian Air Quality, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - Tongass National Forest (100-102), 1989-1992 and undated (Box CLE-33)
      - Tropical Forestry Action Plan (101), 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Utah Wilderness Act (100-102), 1989-1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Western N.C. Wilderness (101), 1990-1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Wood Preserver Issues (102), 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Animal Welfare Act, 1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Biomedical Research Caucus, 1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Steel-Jaw Leghold Traps (101), 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Veal Calf Protection (102), 1991 (Box CLE-33)
      - Vets/FDA [Food and Drug Administration] Labeling (102), 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Elderly Talking Points, undated (Box CLE-33)
      - Emergency Medical Services, 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Cancer, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Cancer-Breast, 1992 and undated (Box CLE-33)
      - Cancer Center Panel Discussion, 1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - Cancer DES [Diethystilbestrol], 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Community Health Centers, 1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Diabetes, 1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Domestic Violence, 1994 (Box CLE-33)
      - Hospice, 1992 and undated (Box CLE-33)
      - Hospitals
        - General, 1989 (Box CLE-33)
        - Admitting Managers, 1992 (Box CLE-33)
        - AHA [American Hospital Association], 1993 (Box CLE-33)
        - NCHA [North Carolina Association of Healthcare and Admitting Managers?], 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - FDA
        - General, 1992 (Box CLE-33)
        - Alzheimer's, Tacrine, Cognex, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-33)
        - Multiple Sclerosis Betaseron, 1994 (Box CLE-33)
        - Breast Implants, 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Fetal Tissue, 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Home Health Care, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-33)
      - MCH [Maternal and Child Health]
        - General, 1991 (Box CLE-33)
        - Access to Obstetrics, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-33)
        - Immunizations, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-33)
        - Infant Mortality, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-33)
        - Infant Mortality Task Force, 1990 and undated (Box CLE-33)
      - Medical Equipment Suppliers, 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Mental Health, 1993 (Box CLE-33)
      - Mental Health ADAMHA [Alcohol, Drug Abuse and Mental Health Administration], 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - Mental Health-ARC [Association for Retarded Citizens], 1987 and undated (Box CLE-33)
      - NIH [National Institutes of Health], 1992 (Box CLE-33)
      - NHSC [National Health Service Corps], 1990 (Box CLE-34)
      - Ryan White Care Act, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Nurses, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Nutrition, 1990 (Box CLE-34)
      - Organ Donors, 1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Physicians
        - AMA, 1991 (Box CLE-34)
        - Asheboro Medical Society, 1989-1992 (Box CLE-34)
        - Primary Care, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Public Health, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - RU-486, 1991 (Box CLE-34)
      - Sex Survey-DP Speech and TP, 1991 and undated (Box CLE-34)
      - Sex Survey-Ron Rindfuss, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-34)
      - STD [Sexually Transmitted Disease], 1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Medicaid-Voluntary Contributions, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Amendments (1993), 1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Catastrophic Care, 1989 (Box CLE-34)
      - Flu Program, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Funding Shortfall, 1991 (Box CLE-34)
      - Medigap, undated (Box CLE-34)
      - Medigap Counseling, 1990 (Box CLE-34)
      - Mental Health, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - New Physician Rates, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - PRO [Peer Review Organization]-Dr. James Bryan, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Physician Reimbursement (RBRYS), 1990 (Box CLE-34)
      - Radiologists-NC Conversion Factor, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Regulatory Relief (101st), 1990 and undated (Box CLE-34)
      - Canadian-Style [Health Care], undated (Box CLE-34)
      - Children, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Children and Pregnant Women, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Children and Women-Academy of Pediatrics, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Consumers-Encore, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Consumers-Fair Share, 1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Drugs (Unitary Pricing), 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Pharmacy/Drugs, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Employer Mandate, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - ERISA and National Reform, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - General-Reform [Health Care], 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - HMOs and Managed Care Plans, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Insurance Brokers, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Malpractice, 1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Medicare, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Medical Research Fund, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Medical Society, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Small Business, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Stark (Ways and Means), 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Speeches (Miscellaneous) and Talking Points, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - N.C. Health Contacts, undated (Box CLE-34)
      - Women's Health (Women's Issues), 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - Worker's Compensation, 1994 (Box CLE-34)
      - SE [Southeast] Low-level Compact (100-102), 1987-1992 (Box CLE-34)
      - Low-Level Waste/NC (103), 1993 (Box CLE-34)
      - Yucca Mountain-High-Level Waste (100-102), 1991 (Box CLE-34)
      - Health Care Forum-North Carolina State University, 1994, 1 of 2 folders (Box CLE-34)
      - Health Care Forum-North Carolina State University, 1994, 2 of 2 folders (Box CLE-35)
      - Cable Television (E and C), 1992-1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - Cable, 1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - Cable Act-One-Time Fee, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - FCC [Federal Communications Commission]-Per-Line/Per-Call, Caller-ID Blocking, 1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - Tel. Brooks-Dingell HR 3626, 1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - 900 Numbers, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - HR 417-Rep. Tauzin-Securities Reform Act (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - Info Services-Alarm Industry, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-35)
      - Northern Telecom, 1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - WCPE Radio, 1989-1992, 2 folders (Box CLE-35)
      - WUNC, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - FY '90-Int. App.-NEA [National Endowment for the Arts]-Helms Amendment, 1989 (Box CLE-35)
      - MFJ-Cooper Info Services, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - Semans Request re NEA Art Review Board, 1989 (Box CLE-35)
      - Brunswick Nuclear Plant, 1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - Duke Power/General, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - Efficient Lighting, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - FEMA [Federal Emergency Management Agency] Fee for Nuclear Plants, 1994 (Box CLE-35)
      - Lab Waste Equity Act (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-35)
      - ALMR [Advanced Liquid Metal Reactor] [Program], 1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - EMF [Electric and Magnetic Fields] (101), 1991 (Box CLE-36)
      - Energy Bill/HR 776 (102), 1992 (Box CLE-36)
      - National Energy Policy/Bush Administration, 1991 (Box CLE-36)
      - Ethanol/Reg-Neg [Regulatory Negotiation] (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Hydrogen and Fusion/HR 4908 (103), 1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Nuclear Power/Miscellaneous Co-Sponsored Bills, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-36)
      - Petroleum Marketing/HR 2966 (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-36)
      - H. Con. Res. 188/Sharp Resolution (103), 1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Shearon-Harris Nuclear Plant, 1987-1992 (Box CLE-36)
      - Scientific Fraud at Duke University, 1989 (Box CLE-36)
      - Utility Transmission Access (100-102), 1990-1992 (Box CLE-36)
      - Lab Waste (103), 1992-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - High-Level Nuclear Waste Facility (103), 1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - N.C. Hazardous Waste Incinerator (102), 1990-1991 (Box CLE-36)
    - Foreign Affairs Subseries, 1986-1994 and undated
      Relates to international issues and political efforts, and contains a higher percentage of correspondence to and from White House officials, including George Bush (Sr.), James A. Baker, III, and Bill Clinton. Other frequent correspondents include foreign dignitaries, officials in the U.S. Department of State, and the Congressional Human Rights Caucus. Prominent topics include: the Persian Gulf War; Israel; Iraq; human rights issues; asylum for particular individuals (e.g. Joseph Doherty); foreign aid, especially to the former Soviet Union; and American Scott J. Nelson. In addition to documents generated or received by Price's office, there are a number of speeches by various VIPs. Arranged roughly by country.
      - Aid to Former Soviet Union/E. European Nations, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - DP's Foreign Affairs Letters, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-36)
      - Foreign Aid Authorization-1994, 1993 (Box CLE-36)
      - Lucille Bloch, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Carnivore Preservation Trust, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - MBA Enterprise Corps, 1993 (Box CLE-36)
      - National Endowment for Democracy, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-36)
      - Torture Victim Protection Act, undated (Box CLE-36)
      - Foreign Affairs: General, undated (Box CLE-36)
      - International Family Planning, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Albania, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Argentina, 1991 (Box CLE-36)
      - Armenia/Azerbaijan, 1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - The Baltics (Lithuania, Latvia, and Estonia), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Cambodia, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-36)
      - China, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Cuba, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1990 (Box CLE-36)
      - Eastern Europe, General, 1992 (Box CLE-36)
      - El Salvador, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-36)
      - German Study Group, 1987-1993 (Box CLE-36)
      - Greece/Cyprus, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-36)
      - Guatemala, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Haiti, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Haiti Resolution, 1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Honduras, 1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - The Horn-Ethiopia, Somalia, and Sudan, 1991 (Box CLE-37)
      - India, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Caucus on India and Indian-Americans, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Indonesia, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Iran, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Iraq, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Israel, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Japan, 1992 (Box CLE-37)
      - Lebanon, 1990-1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Nicaragua, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - North Atlantic Assembly, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Pakistan, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Panama, 1992 and undated (Box CLE-37)
      - Persian Gulf, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-37)
      - Poland/Hungary, 1989-1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Romania, 1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Saudi Arabia, 1992 (Box CLE-37)
      - Somalia, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - South Africa, 1988-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Sudan, 1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Syria, 1993 (Box CLE-37)
      - Taiwan, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - Thailand, 1992 (Box CLE-37)
      - Turkey, 1992 (Box CLE-37)
      - United Nations, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-37)
      - USSR and Beyond (Commonwealth of Independent States), 1991-1994 (Box CLE-38)
      - Vietnam, 1992-1993 (Box CLE-38)
      - Yugoslavia, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-38)
      - Speech Material, 1991 and undated (Box CLE-38)
      - Human Rights/General, 1991-1994, 3 folders (Box CLE-38)
      - Africa/Human Rights, 1990-1991 (Box CLE-38)
      - N. Africa/Human Rights, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-38)
      - China/Tibet-Human Rights, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-38)
      - E. Europe/Human Rights, 1990 (Box CLE-38)
      - Korea/Human Rights, 1990-1991 (Box CLE-38)
      - Middle East/Human Rights, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-38)
      - SE [Southeast] Asia/Human Rights, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-38)
      - South and Central America/Human Rights, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-38)
      - Soviet Union/Human Rights, 1990-1991 (Box CLE-38)
      - Doherty Asylum, 1986-1992, 2 folders (Box CLE-38)
      - Nelson, Scott, 1991-1994 (Box CLE-39)
      - Iraq, 1983-1991, 2 folders (Box CLE-39)
    - Government Operations Subseries, 1985-1993 and undated
      This small group of files includes documents related to federal funding and payment, as well as government efficiency and performance. Burroughs Wellcome, and the EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] are prominent. Formats include memos and correspondence.
      - Burroughs Wellcome-HIV Drugs, 1990-1991 (Box CLE-39)
      - Chief Financial Officers, 1985 and undated (Box CLE-39)
      - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] Cabinet Level (101), 1990 and undated (Box CLE-39)
      - Prompt Payment (100), 1988 (Box CLE-39)
      - Recycling, U.S. House, 1991 and undated (Box CLE-39)
      - Government Operations/General, undated (Box CLE-39)
      - Government Operations/Paperwork Reduction, 1993 (Box CLE-39)
      - Government Operations/HR 826/Government Performance, 1993 (Box CLE-39)
    - House Administration Subseries, 1990-1994
      Centers on topics such as campaign finance reform legislation and chair of the committee, Sam Gejdenson. Frequent correspondents include congressional colleagues and Common Cause. The Committee on House Administration also figures prominently in these files. The files are unarranged.
      - Campaign Finance, 1990-1994 (Box CLE-39)
    - Judiciary Subseries, 1985-1994